<resources>
    <string name="app_name">2112500851_AplikasiGabungan_AF</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">MapsActivity</string>
    <string name="content_lollipop">Android Lollipop (codenamed Android L during development) is the fifth major version of the Android mobile operating system developed by Google and the 12th version of Android, spanning versions between 5.0 and 5.1.1.[4] Unveiled on June 25, 2014 at the Google I/O 2014 conference, it became available through official over-the-air (OTA) updates on November 12, 2014, for select devices that run distributions of Android serviced by Google (such as Nexus and Google Play edition devices). Its source code was made available on November 3, 2014. The first phone with Android Lollipop was Nexus 6.</string>
    <string name="content_marshmallow">Android Marshmallow (codenamed Android M during development) is the sixth major version of the Android operating system and the 13th version of Android. First released as a beta build on May 28, 2015, it was officially released on September 29, 2015, with the Nexus devices being the first to receive the update. The first devices released with Android Marshmallow were the Nexus 5X and Nexus 6P.</string>
    <string name="content_nougat">Android Nougat (codenamed Android N during development) is the seventh major version and 14th original version of the Android operating system. First released as an alpha test version on March 9, 2016, it was officially released on August 22, 2016, with Nexus devices being the first to receive the update. The LG V20 was the first smartphone released with Nougat.</string>
    <string name="content_oreo">Android Oreo (codenamed Android O during development) is the eighth major release and the 15th version of the Android mobile operating system. It was first released as an alpha quality developer preview in March 2017 and released to the public on August 21, 2017. It contains a number of major features, including notification grouping, picture-in-picture support for video, performance improvements, and battery usage optimization, and support for autofillers, Bluetooth 5, system-level integration with VoIP apps, wide color gamuts, and Wi-Fi Aware. Android Oreo also introduces two major platform features: Android Go – a software distribution of the operating system for low-end devices – and support for implementing a hardware abstraction layer.</string>
    <string name="content_pie">Android Pie (codenamed Android P during development), also known as Android 9 (API 28) is the ninth major release and the 16th version of the Android mobile operating system. It was first released as a developer preview on March 7, 2018, and was released publicly on August 6, 2018. On August 6, 2018, Google officially announced the final release of Android 9 under the title "Pie", with the update initially available for current Google Pixel devices, and releases for Android One devices and others to follow "later this year".</string>
    <string name="content_q">Android 10 (codenamed Android Q during development) is the tenth major release and the 17th version of the Android mobile operating system. It was first released as a developer preview on March 13, 2019, and was released publicly on September 3, 2019.Android 10 was officially released on September 3, 2019, for supported Google Pixel devices, as well as the third-party Essential Phone and Redmi K20 Pro in selected markets. The OnePlus 7T was the first device with Android 10 pre-installed. In October 2019, it was reported that Google certification requirements for Google Mobile Services will only allow Android 10-based builds to be approved after January 31, 2020.</string>
    <string name="content_redvelvet">Android 11 is the eleventh major release and 18th version of Android, the mobile operating system developed by the Open Handset Alliance led by Google. It was released on September 8, 2020. The first phone launched in Europe with Android 11 was the Vivo X51 5G and after its full stable release, the first phone in the world which came with Android 11 after Google Pixel 5 was OnePlus 8T. According to 9 to 5 Google, as of May 2022, Android 11 has become the most popular version of the OS with a share of 28.3 percent. This was up 4 percent since November 2021 (both on smartphones and tablets).</string>
    <string name="content_snowcone">Android 12 is the twelfth major release and 19th version of Android, the mobile operating system developed by the Open Handset Alliance led by Google. The first beta was released on May 18, 2021. Android 12 was released publicly on October 4, 2021, through Android Open Source Project (AOSP) and was released to supported Google Pixel devices on October 19, 2021. Android 12 is the third most popular Android version on smartphones at 11.97%. The first phones to have Android 12 were the Google Pixel 6 and the Pixel 6 Pro.</string>
    <string name="content_tiramisu">Google released the stable Android 13 update to the public on August 15, 2022. The update was made available to the company Pixel phones alongside the source code. Google Developer Preview program for Android 13 started in February 2022 and a lot has changed since then, leading up to the final release in August 2022.</string>


</resources>